This time a year
ago we just had
the deep seek moment
and everyone was incredibly
excited about what happened
there And there was
still a you that
Google DeepMind was kind
of lagging OpenAI I
would say that now
it's looking quite different
I they've declared code
red right It's been
quite a year So
talk me through what
specifically you've been surprised
by and how well
you've done this year
and whether you think
And then I'm to
ask you about the
line up Well look
I think we were
I was always very
confident we would get
back to sort the
top of the leaderboards
and the SOTA type
of across the because
I think we've always
had the deepest and
broadest research bench And
it was about kind
marshalling that all together
and getting the
and focus and the
kind start up mentality
back to the whole
organisation And it's been
a lot of work
but I think we're
still a lot of
work to do but
I think you can
start seeing the you
the kind of the
progress that's been made
in both the models
with Gemini 3 but
also on the product
side with Gemini app
getting increasing market share
So I feel like
we're making great progress
but there's a tonne
more work to do